barclaysstockbrokers.co.uk 2017-02-02

# Privacy Policy - Barclays Stockbrokers

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully before using this website ("the Site"). In this Policy "we", "us" and "our" means Barclays Bank PLC and "you" means the individual who is using the Site. By using our Site, you agree with the collection, storage, use and the disclosure of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

We may change the content found on the Site at any time without notice, and consequently our Privacy Policy may change at any time in the future. You should read the Privacy Policy each time you use the Site, as access to or use of the Site means that you agree to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect when you use the site. 

Our Privacy Policy, together with the Important Information sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  Your personal data will be processed in accordance with applicable law and regulation. Accordingly, for the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act"), the data controller is Barclays Bank PLC. For the purposes of the Act, any member of the Barclays Group (defined below) may be our nominated representative. 

This policy contains the following sub-headings: 

  * ###   
Cookies 

With regards to the new requirements on cookies following the revision of the e-Privacy Directive, Barclays is working towards implementing the new requirements in line with guidance from the Information Commissioner's Office.

To make using our Site as straightforward as possible and to improve the service we offer you, we use cookies. 

Back to top

### How will we use the information we collect about you? 

We will store and process your information on the Barclays Group computers wherever located (including outside the European Economic Area (EEA)) and in any other medium. By "your information" we mean personal and financial information we:  

(a) obtain from you or from third parties and other organisations when you apply for an account or any other product or service for which you or they give to us at any other time; or  
(b) learn from the way you use and manage your account(s), from the transactions made, if any, such as the date, amount, currency and the name and type of supplier (e.g. supermarket services, medical services, retail services). 

By "Barclays Group" we mean subsidiaries of Barclays Bank PLC (as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985). We and other companies in the Barclays Group will use your information to manage your account(s), give you statements and provide our services, for assessment and analysis (including credit and/or behaviour scoring, market and product analysis), to identify and tackle fraud, money laundering and other crime, carry out regulatory checks and meet our obligations to any relevant regulatory authority, and to develop and improve our services to you and other customers and protect our interests. 

We and other members of the Barclays Group may use your information for marketing purposes. If you don't want us to tell you about other products and services, please write to us and supply us with your full name and address and details of any products or services you have with us. Please write to your normal point of contact, or your Relationship Manager. Alternatively, [contact us. ](https://apps.barclaysstockbrokers.co.uk/ContactUs "Contact us")

Back to top

### Will we share your information with anyone else? 

**Will we share your information with anyone else?**

We may share your information including how you manage your account or Site visit with other companies within the Barclays Group and/or to relevant third parties and as permitted by law including but not limited to the following:   

•    People who provide a service to us or are acting as our agents, on the understanding that they will keep the information confidential.   
•    Anyone to whom we transfer or may transfer all or any part of our business or assets, from whom we acquire any business or assets or who acquires substantially all of the assets of Barclays Bank PLC.   
•    Credit reference and fraud prevention agencies.  
•    We may also give out information about you if we have a duty to do so in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our [terms of use](http://www.barclayswealth.com/important-information.htm "terms of use") or if the law allows us to do so.

If we disclose your information to a service provider (a person, office or organisation) located in another country (including locations outside of the European Economic Area), we will take steps reasonably necessary to ensure that they apply the same levels of protection as we are required to apply to your information and to use your information only for the purpose of providing the service to us. By submitting your personal information you agree to this transfer. 

Back to top

### How long will we keep your personal information on file? 

We will retain information about you after the closure of your account or service provision for as long as it is permitted for legal, regulatory, fraud prevention, business and financial crime purposes. 

Back to top

We will retain information about you after the closure of your account or service provision for as long as it is permitted for legal, regulatory, fraud prevention, business and financial crime purposes. 

### Electronic communications 

Please remember that internet communications are not secure unless the data being sent is encrypted. We cannot accept any responsibility for the unauthorised access by a third party and/or the corruption of data being sent by individuals to the Barclays Group. It is your responsibility to determine whether you need to encrypt your data before sending. 

Back to top

### Intellectual Property 

The entire content of the Site is subject to copyright with all rights reserved and it may only be stored, held or used for your personal use only. You may not download (all or in part) for non-personal use or otherwise reproduce, transmit or modify the Site without our prior permission. However, you may print out part or all of the Site for your own personal use. These permissions are revocable by us at any time. 

Barclays and Barclays Wealth are registered trade marks owned by Barclays Bank PLC. You are granted a non-exclusive licence of those rights in order to view this site on a non-commercial basis only, revocable at any time. 

Back to top

### Security 

It has always been our policy that if any of our clients are victims of unauthorised access to their accounts we will cover any resulting direct financial loss which the client suffers provided that the client has not breached our security procedures. 

You must ensure that viruses, trojans, worms or equivalent or similar items do not enter your computer system. We assume no responsibility for loss of whatever nature, howsoever arising, resulting from such viruses, trojans, worms or equivalent or similar items. 

For further information and advice on security, please click on Security. 

### 

### Calls 

We may record and monitor calls made or received by us to maintain high quality service standards, to check instructions, for your protection and ours, and for regulatory reasons. 

Back to top

### Your Queries 

If you have any queries regarding privacy issues then please [email us](mailto:priv.acy@barclayswealth.com "Email us"), or write to us at Barclays Wealth, Data Protection Officer, 1 Churchill Place, Risk – Level 16, Canary Wharf, London, United Kingdom E14 5HP. 

Back to top

### External Links 

All of the external sites you can reach through Barclays Wealth Online are here to help you. However, we must tell you that we accept no responsibility or liability for the content, accuracy or availability of any external site you may encounter. 

Back to top

### Compliance Reporting

When you instruct us to provide Compliance Reporting to a Company (or their appoint representative),  the information will be transmitted in accordance with Barclays Privacy Policy, which is updated regularly and can be found on this page. This information may change from time to time. Information we consider relevant to personal account dealing includes but is not limited to, account transactions, holdings and related personal information. 

You should instruct us on each Barclays Stockbrokers Account you hold separately.  If we establish that you have more than one Account but you have not specified that it should be included in the Employee Trading Reports, we may provide information to the Company, on all such account(s).

The Company may tell us that the employee to which the reports relate have left their employment. Should you want us to stop reporting on your Account(s) you must contact us to do so.

The Company will process the information received in accordance with their own policies and this may mean that your data is processed outside of the United Kingdom. Barclays Stockbrokers will only send data to jurisdictions where we are confident similar Data Privacy legislations would be applied as here in the United Kingdom. For more information on how your data will be processed and the implications, please refer to your employers PA Dealing Policy or contact your Compliance / HR function. 

View a list of all employers this service supports. This list may change from time to time and any employer can be removed from the service at the discretion of Barclays or that employer. This service is provided at the request and convenience of the employer to support their regulatory and or policy requirements. If an employer is no longer a participant of this service, Barclays will reduce the information provided to the employer by  issuing a copy contract note only. Therefore, the employer may require further information directly from you the employee/account holder.

Back to top

### Your Queries 

If you have any queries regarding privacy issues then please [email us](mailto:priv.acy@barclayswealth.com "Email us"), or write to us at Barclays Wealth, Data Protection Officer, 1 Churchill Place, Risk – Level 16, Canary Wharf, London, United Kingdom E14 5HP. 

Back to top
